

# Charlotte Guldbæk Interaction Designer

9000 Aalborg, Denmark email: cmguldbaek@gmail.com www.linkedin.com/in/cguldbaek

## Who is Charlotte? .....

I don't like the idea of defining myself by my study, but the aspects of interaction design describe my interests pretty well: UX research, because I find people and their needs and habits super interesting; computer science, because I also find it interesting to learn about what we interact with, and how it works; and last, but not least, there is the creative aspect, allowing me to come up with concepts and communicate them to others.

# IT Competences

# Programming

- HTML & CSS
- (
- C#

# Wireframing

- Figma
- Adobe XD
- Balsamiq

## Illustration

- Procreate
- Photoshop
- Gimp

## Other

- Microsoft Office programs
- Google drive

# Education

2021-now:

MSc in Interaction Design (Aalborg University)

Thesis in collaboration with LEGO
 Skills: System development; entrepreneurship;
 Agile methodology

2018-2021:

BSc in Interaction Design (Aalborg University)

• Bachelor Thesis in collaboration with MuteBox Skills: Wireframing and prototyping; interviewing and field studies; user evaluations

2013-2016:

STX (Aalborg Katedralskole)

• English, Social studies, Media studies

# Work Experience

2017-now:

### Student Assistant (Waoo)

- Regression testing with focus on UI
- Meetings
- Experience with Microsoft Excel
- General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR) certificate

2022:

### Teaching Assistant in System Analysis and Design (AAU)

• Helping with exercises and assignments regarding system development, e.g., system definitions, class diagrams, use cases

2021:

### Teaching Assistant in User-Centred Design (AAU)

- Preparing exercises for the students
- Answering questions regarding data gathering and analysis

# Volunteer Work

2021-now:

### Vice President, i-Life Aalborg

- In charge of meetings
- Planning and executing events for international students
- SoMe

# Language Competences .....

• Danish (native)

English (fluent)

Italian (basics)

German (basics)

## Free Time .....

I love learning new things and getting good at them. It sounds cliché, but I love seeing improvement in my drawing skills, just like I feel a certain pride when I notice my progress in understanding Italian as self-taught. My interest in learning new languages may have a connection to my interest in seeing the world and its cultures.

Though I love experiencing other countries, I also love a good night in. To me, an ideal evening could just as well consist of having a couple of friends over for dinner and a glass of wine, followed by, for instance, a board game. (I won't say no to a karaoke night either)